如果你和每个姑娘都录像
I just don't want to make one of these tapes.
那我还是算了
if it's something you do with every girl.
每个姑娘 当然不会 我可不是冠希老师
Every girl? No, no. I am strictly a one-woman guy.
我可不想自导自演艳照门
Well, I don't want to end up all over the Internet.
我一直是以低调自诩
I pride myself on keeping a low profile.
我的私生活绝不张扬
My private life is private.
等等 我以为你从来没拍过 这些是什么
Wait. I thought you never did this before. What are all these?
哦 那些只是我借来的电影
Oh, uh, just some movies I rented.
「我和布兰迪 传教士体位」
"Me and Brandy, Missionary"?
那是关于两个女孩成为尼姑的故事
A tale of two girls who become nuns.
「我和布兰迪 狗趴式」
"Me and Brandy, Doggy"?
那是续集 讲的是尼姑们养了
The sequel. The nuns.
一只棕色拉布拉多
adopt a chocolate lab.
那些又是什么
What are all those?
哦 那些是标准的
Oh, that's just your standard.
家用安保设备 很常见的
home security setup. Basic run-of-the mill.
没什么大不了的 很多家庭都有
No big deal, nothing too elaborate. Everybody has them.
那怎么都对着你的床
And why do you need security cameras pointing at your bed?
以防小偷偷我的性爱录像带
In case a burglar tries to steal my sex tapes.
我们上床吧
Now, let's get into bed.
我们要速战速决 我明早还要出席一个庭审
Let's just make this quick. I have a court hearing in the morning.
亨德森法官主持的
Judge Henderson?
不是 是他就好了 是汤姆森
No. I wish. Thompson.
嗯 那你有得好受了
Mm. That's going to suck for you.
是关于驾驶事故的 小事一件
It was a driving mishap thingy.
帮我个忙好吗 保证你再也不开车了
Do me a favor. Promise me you won't drive.
你真好 你是在担心我吗
That's sweet. You're worried about me driving.
我是在担心我自己 我可是行人
Mm-mm. I'm worried about me. I'm a pedestrian.
抱歉 是我的提神醒脑器
Sorry. That's my sobriety monitor.
抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
是绑在脚踝上的跟踪脚环
Ankle. Tracking bracelet.
哦 等等 抱歉 是…
Oh, wait. Wait. Sorry, just…
- 这尼玛谁弄的 - 我自己
- Who put that on you? - I did.
只用这样我才能够满足
It's the only way I can have an orgasm.
今晚会是例外
Not tonight.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我… 在热身
Just… warming up.
你确定房子里就我们俩
You sure we're alone here?
总觉得这里还有别人
Feels like there's somebody else in this house.
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
没什么
That's nothing.
那这又是什么
OK, what is that?
只是… 有人在放旧软管而已
Just… unraveling the old hose.
明天再收拾吧 劳尔
Save it for tomorrow, Raul.
好滴 先森
Si, senor.
爽死我了
Wow. That was amazing.
查理
Charlie.
出去 艾米丽奥
Get out of here, Emilio.
查理 我好怕怕
Charlie, I'm scared.
林德熙 亲爱的 没什么可怕的
Lindsay, sweetie, there's nothing to be afraid of.
我这有事 晚点再打给你 伙计
Hey, I got the stuff. I got to call you back, man.
我想我还是走吧
I think I better go.
真的要走 明天再来好不好 你很忙吗
Really? How about tomorrow? You busy?
我要干翻你
I'm going to blow you across the room.
碉堡了
Sounds awesome.
《惊声尖笑5》
（警方于3月15日发现了查理的尸体）
（他的遗体直到23日才停止活塞运动）
（警方正在搜寻查理失踪了的三个孩子 出于习惯他们逮捕了林德熙·罗翰）
故事就此开始
And thus our story begins.
悬赏查理孩子的大笔赏金
The large reward offered for the rescue of Charlie's kids.
吸引了警察 私家侦探
drew the attention of police, private detectives.
以及红十字会志愿者
and Red Cross volunteers.
所有人都急切地搜寻着这几个孩子
Everyone was on high alert for these children,
但这两个人除外
except these two guys.
不对 伙计 奥巴马医改让老年公民
No, man, Obamacare gives senior citizens.
能够获得更便宜的药物
access to cheaper drugs,
免费的预防保健
free preventative care,
而且弥补了医疗保险处方药计划的漏洞
and it closes the Medicare Part D loophole.
那如果把洗发露弄到马眼里了这些又有什么用
And how does that help if I get shampoo in my dick hole?
- 啥 - 你敢说你从来没有把洗发露
- What? - Mean to tell me you ain't never got.
- 弄进去过吗 - 好吧
- shampoo in your pee hole? - OK.
- 也许有那么一两次 - 是啊 一两次
- Maybe like once or twice. - Yeah, once or twice.
就在你瞎撸的时候
when you was playing with yourself.
没有 我没有瞎撸
No, I wasn't playing with myself.
我是在洗澡 就一不小心弄进去了
I was showering, and crazy got up in there.
扯淡 牛顿的万有引力定律是这样的
Bullshit. Cam Newton's law of gravity is:
你那玩意儿不翘起来 肥皂水是进不去的
That thing must be up in order for that soap to go down.
不管怎么说 那真是疼死了
Well, either way, that shit stings like hell.
确实很疼 就像里面一只蜜蜂发现自己的女人
Sting like a mother, man, it feel like it's a hornet up in there.
在和别的男人乱搞 然后猛地蛰了你一下
And he found out his girl be, you know, doing her thing with another man.
- 没错 - 我搞不懂
- Exactly. - I don't understand why.
洗发露公司不能处理这个问题 伙计
the shampoo company can't fix that, man.
他们能做出「无泪配方」
They got "No More Tears."
为什么就不能发明个鸡爽配方
Why they can't make no more hornets in your dick?
我觉得他们想不到你会把
I don't really think they expect you.
无泪洗发露用在鸡巴上
to use the No More Tears on your dick.
那他们为什么叫强生
Well, why they call it Johnson & Johnson?
我有个更好的问题 伙计 我们两个大男人
I got a better question, man. What the hell are two stoners doing.
在这片阴森森的森林里瞎逛是干什么
wandering around these spooky-ass woods?
听着 会有回报的
Look, it's going to be worth it.
我告诉过你… 这里是洪堡郡
I told you… this is Humboldt County.
这里是他们种毒品的地方
This is where all the growers grow their bomb-ass shit.
你觉得他们会让我们随便拿
You think they're gonna be cool with us just helping ourselves?
我们不用带走整株植物
Look, man, we ain't taking no plants.
剪几片叶子就行 你懂我意思吗
We're gonna snip a few buds. You know what I'm saying?
然后叶子就会像龙虾一样重新长大
It's gonna grow back just like a lobster paw.
植物就是这样的
You know, that's how nature do.
我不这么认为 伙计 总觉得不太对
I don't know, man. Just doesn't feel right.
他们不会在意的 我们会没事
Man, they ain't gonna care. Look, man, we're gonna be cool.
我们捞一票 然后就离开这
We're gonna roll one blunt, then we're gonna get up out of here.
- 一票 - 就一票
- Just one? - Just one.
- 他们无所谓吗 - 只管跑 伙计
- They won't care, huh? - Man, just keep running.
我勒个擦 那是无人机吗 我们不是本拉登啊
Holy shit. Is that a drone? They're going all Zero Dark Thirty on our ass.
我觉得他们走了
Yo, I think they gone.
树林里有个小屋 我们得过去躲一躲
Oh, whoa. It's a cabin in the woods. We need to go hide over in there.
不行 伙计 我才不要
Nah, man, I'm not going in there.
这让我想起我看过的一部恐怖电影
It reminds me of a horror movie I once saw.
什么恐怖电影
What horror movie?
讲树林中有一个小屋的电影
The one with the cabin in the woods.
- 黑色星期五 - 不是
- Friday the 13th? - No.
是讲树林中有一个小屋的电影
The one with the cabin in the woods.
德州电锯杀人狂
Texas Chain Saw Massacre?
不是 是讲树林中有一个小屋的电影
No, the one with the cabin in the woods.
午夜凶铃
The Ring.
是讲树林中有一个小屋的电影
The one with the cabin in the woods.
女巫布莱尔
Blair Witch Project.
不是 伙计 是讲树林中有一个小屋的电影
No, man, the one with the cabin in the woods.
- 明斯特一家 - 这部不是在树林里的
- The Munsters. - That wasn't in the woods.
- 这部连电影都不算 - 听着 伙计
- They wasn't even a damn movie. - Look, man,
我们没时间在这里闲扯
we ain't got time for this shit right now.
我们得进树林里那间屋子
We need to get to that cabin in the woods.
那他妈是什么声音
What the hell is that sound?
听起来是房屋沉降的声音
Sound like the house settling.
但这里看其来挺新的
It looked new.
- 我去看看 - 去吧
- I'm gonna take a look around. - Go ahead.
啊 那是什么
Ah! What is that?
- 我们在射什么 - 那个
- Where we shooting? - There.
- 哪个 - 阴影
- Where? - The dark!
- 那儿 - 不 是那片阴影
- There? - No, this dark.
在那儿
Over there.
那是什么
Dude, what the hell was that?
巨型阿拉斯加帝王蟹刚爬到我身上了
Big-ass Alaskan king crab just ran up on me, man.
- 蟹 你找死 - 你试试
- Crab? Cuz, we banging? - Ja'Marcus,
- 把枪放下 伙计 - 你先放 小子
- put the guns down, man. - Put yours down first, homey.
好吧 一起数三 一 二 三
All right, on three. One, two, three.
艹 你还想来一遍
Damn. You want to try it again?
当然 一 二 三
Sure. One, two, three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
一 奥 散
Uno, dos, tres.
我们可以这样玩一整天 伙计
Man, we could do this shit all day.
- 停战 - 停战
- Truce? - Truce.
迪安得雷 你看 只是两个小女孩而已
Hey, yo, D'Andre. Look, homey. It's two little girls.
他们是种族主义者 伙计
They're little racist girls, man.
涂了一脸黑 没关系吗
Wearing blackface. Cool with that?
嘿 小妹妹 你叫什么名字
Hey, little girl, what's your name?
- 她说什么 - 她说「我想尝尝你的腿」
- What'd she say? - She said, "I wonder what your leg.
- 「不知味道如何」 - 啥 啊 我擦
- tastes like." - What? Ah, man!
这小蜘蛛女咬了我一口
Little spider girl bit me.
你可能要有超能力了
Maybe you're going to get superpowers.
- 我可不是什么黑超人 - 交给我
- Ain't no black superheroes. - I'm on it.
你妹啊
' Hi-ya!
迪安得雷 我觉得她们是新闻里说的失踪女孩
Yo. D'Andre, I think they're the missing kids from the news.
- 你为什么这么肯定 - 你看
- How can you be so sure? - Look.
我也不敢肯定 但如果她们真是失踪儿童
I don't know, man. Well, if it is the missing kids,
我就会拿到一笔奖金 然后给自己买
I'm gonna take that reward money, and I'm gonna buy me.
一艘游艇 装满现金和妹子 再养一条鲨鱼
a yacht, fill it with cash, bitches and a shark.
你养鲨鱼做什么
Why would you want to buy a shark?
相信我… 我们会用得上的
Trust me… we're gonna need a shark.
不 这不可能
No, this can't be right.
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
我回头再打给你
I got to call you back.
别怀孕 别怀孕 别怀孕
No baby, no baby, no baby, no baby.
- 你怀孕了 - 不
- You're pregnant… - No!
但这是爱怀孕测试的数据结果
…with anticipation over the outcome of this iPregnancy test,
这一结果表明…
which has determined that you are…
坑爹呢
You got to be kidding me.
噢 不
Oh, no.
你没怀孕
Not pregnant.
狗运不错 小荡妇
You dodged a bullet, you lucky slut.
谢天谢地 棒极了
Thank you, God. Sweet!
好消息 他们找到我哥哥的孩子了
Great news: They found my brother's kids.
噢 我擦
Oh, crap.
幸运的是大女儿 凯西
We're very fortunate the older one, Kathy, has retained.
记起了大部分的词汇
most of her vocabulary.
婴儿则一字未说
The baby hasn't actually said a word.
- 怎么会 - 因为他还是个婴儿
- Why not? - Because he's a baby.
他们已经单独待在这三个月了
They've been alone here over three long months.
我得提醒你们这一切并不容易
I need to warn both of you that this is not going to be easy.
我准备好了
I'm ready for it.
- 你好啊 - 不对 不对 不是这扇窗
- Hello. - No, no. Wrong window.
这里才是孩子们的房间
Here's where the children are.
- 她在干什么 - 为了适应
- What is she doing? - In order to survive.
极度孤立的生活 孩子们想象出了一个守护者
their extreme isolation, the girls created an imaginary guardian,
一个喂他们吃饭 唱给给他们听的人
a parent figure to feed them, sing to them.
他们称她为麻麻
They call her Mama.
这也许能帮你们有所进展
But these may help you break through.
利他林也能有所帮助
And the Ritalin may help, as well.
适合他们这个年纪的用量是…
The proper dosage for someone their age is…
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
嘿 莉莉
Hey, Lily.
噢 真可爱
Oh, how cute.
- 好吧 - 凯西
- OK. - Kathy.
没事的 凯西 记得这个吗
It's OK, Kathy. Remember these?
你以前戴的 能帮助你看得更清楚
You used to wear them to help you see better.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
我们也许应该给她配个隐形眼镜 软的那种
Maybe we should get her some contacts… the soft kind.
爸爸
Daddy?
不 亲爱的 我不是你爸爸
No, sweetheart. Not Daddy.
我是你的丹叔叔 你还记得吗
I'm your Uncle Dan. Remember?
这位是朱迪
And this is Jody.
朱…迪
Jo…dy.
朱迪 朱和迪中间没有停顿
Jody. No pause between "Jo" and "dy."
朱…迪
Jo…dy.
丹 教不会了 带回去养肯定要悲剧
Dan, we're at an impasse. I see constant conflict.
没事的 他们会对你敞开心扉的
It's fine. They'll warm up to you.
噢
Oh!
嘿 嘿 嘿 小姑娘 不能这样
Hey, hey, hey, little lady, that's not how…
你个小娘们儿
You little mother!
一切都很合我们的心意 医生 他们看着很乖
Well, everything checks out. They seem like good kids, Doc.
报销下我们的停车费 我们带他们回家
Just validate our parking. We'll take them home.
伙计 事情不是你们想的那样
Folks, I wish it were that easy.
你们不给报销
You don't validate?
我是说你们不能带走那些孩子
I'm saying the kids are not yours to take.
看来没戏了 我们撤吧
Well, you can't win them all. Let's skedaddle.
这没道理 他们是我哥哥查理的孩子
That's not fair. They're my brother Charlie's kids.
我们有合法监护权
We deserve them.
是吗 你的妻子是朋克摇滚乐手 整夜不着家
Do you? Your wife plays in a punk rock band, staying out all night long,
吸毒抽大麻 每晚还和不同男人滚床单
high on drugs, sleeping with a different man every night.
我估计法院不会判给你们
I don't think the courts are gonna look upon that too favorably.
- 但是 - 我只是吓吓你们
- But… - I was just messing with you.
- 他们是你们的了 - 真的吗
- The kids are yours. - They are?
你听见了吗 亲爱的 他们是我们的了
Did you hear that, honey? They're ours!
只有一个附加条件
On one condition.
这栋房子归案例研究所所有
This house is owned by the Institute for Case Studies.
每间房间都装了全方位无死角摄像头
Every room is fully wired with cameras.
你们要搬进房子里才能拥有孩子们
If you move into the house, you get the kids.
我们就不能卖了房子
Can't we just sell the house.
然后把孩子送进高档的孤儿院
and put the kids in a high-end orphanage?
朱迪 你真的准备好当妈妈了吗
Jody, do you really think you're out to be a mom?
- 她当然准备好了 - 丹
- Of course she is. - Dan!
以后 没有摇滚乐队 没有这蠢假发
Now, no more rock band, no more silly wig.
蠢你妹啊 这是我身体的一部分
It's not silly. It's all a part of me.
- 也没有纹身 - 你做什么
- And no more tattoos. - What are you doing?
做我应该做的 我们是标准的郊区小夫妇
What I had to. We're a perfect suburban couple.
于是丹和朱迪带着孩子们向新家出发了
And so Dan and Jody headed to their new house with their new children.
但是 就像是放完春假回学校的联谊会小骚货
But, like a slutty sorority girl returning from spring break,
他们也带回了隐藏在背后的罪恶
they were also bringing home a hidden evil.
好了 孩子们 这是我们的新家
All right, kids, here's our new house.
这是丹叔叔
And here's Uncle Dan.
嗨 别忘了还有妈妈
Hi. Don't forget about mommy!
丹 我不是他们的妈妈
Dan, I'm not their mommy.
他们可以喊我朱迪阿姨
They can call me Aunt Jody.
或者阿朱 J妈 桑德斯太太
Or Jodes, J-Mom, Mrs. Sanders.
或者他们也可以喊我 车库
Or, if they really want to call me… Garage!
这是朱迪和艾丹
Here comes Jody and Aidan,
第一次踏进家门
entering the house for the very first time.
这里就是我们好好保护你
This is where we're going to protect you.
不让你受任何的…
and make sure nothing bad…
哦 天哪 艾丹 抱歉 抱歉
Oh, my God, Aidan! I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
也许我们应该把他放在婴儿篮里
Maybe we should put him in the carrier.
好 好 这样好多了
There, see, that's better.
来吧 艾丹 怎么了 怎么了
Come on, Aidan. What, what, what?
- 放轻松 没事的 - 哦 完蛋了
- Relax, it's OK. - Oh, my gosh.
- 丹 孩子不见了 - 什么
- Dan, I lost the baby! - What?
哦 天哪 艾丹 艾丹 你在哪里
Oh, my gosh, Aidan! Aidan, where are you?!
- 艾丹 - 他去哪里了
- Aidan! - Where did he go?
哦 他在这儿
Oh, there he is, OK.
这是你姐姐凯西
Here's your sister Kathy.
哦 艾丹 没事的
Oh, Aidan, it's OK.
你只需要用婴儿的语气说话
You've just got to talk in a baby voice.
- 你说的内容反而不重要 - 好吧
- It doesn't even matter what you say. - OK.
我是你继母妈咪
I'm your stepmommy.
不是你的死鬼妈咪
I'm not your fricking mommy.
表现不错 你很有天赋
There you go, you're a natural.
你闻到了吗
What's that smell?
哦 我的天 我该怎么办 哦 哦 用这个
Oh, my God, what do I do? Oh, oh! Here, this, hold on!
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan!
- 凯西 哦 抱歉 宝贝 - 哎哟哇
- Kathy! Oh, sorry, honey - Ow!
好啦 完成啦 亲爱的
All right, there you go, sweetie.
这里是不是有点阴气逼人
Is it chilly in here?
我一进房间就感觉到了
I felt it as soon as I entered the room.
没有啊 嘿 这些是什么
Feels fine. Hey, what are these?
这些很有趣 这是什么
This is interesting. What is this?
我不知道 那是麻麻画的
I don't know, Mama drew that one.
看 这是我们画的艾丹
Look, we drew this picture for Aidan.
这是艾丹坐着火箭飞向月球
See? It's Aidan on a rocket to the moon.
- 哦 坐在火箭上 - 莉莉呢
- Oh. Sitting on a rocket. - Where's Lily?
哦 不 亲爱的 换一头
Oh, no, sweetie, the other end.
噢
Ooh!
我们把艾丹介绍给其余的家庭成员吧
Let's go introduce Aidan to the rest of the family.
哦 这是我们毛茸茸的家人
Oh, and there's our furry family member.
- 没错 玛利亚 - 才不是呢 是阿迪
- Yes, Maria. - No, Dan, Artie.
哦 对 对 我们的爱犬阿迪
Oh, yes, of course, our dog Artie.
啊 新宝宝 我来为他祈福
Ay, the new baby. I make blessing. Oh.
好了 好了 这就够了 玛利亚
OK, OK, that's good, Maria.
哦 天哪
Oh, my gosh.
多了三个孩子要养活
With three new kids to care for,
丹更需要在工作上有所建树
Dan really needed to start performing at work.
不幸的是他和他的同事处得并不顺利
Unfortunately he was having some issues with a colleague.
凯撒 我有预感你这次能行
OK, Caesar, this is the one, I can feel it.
八十一秒 哦 凯撒
Eighty-one seconds? Oh, Caesar.
这是你有史以来的最差成绩了
That's your worst time yet.
你在创造力测试上的表现更令人失望
You're doing even worse on your creativity test.
你看看我用积木搭出来的这些充满创意的作品
I mean, look at all the imaginative things I made out of blocks.
比如这架飞机
Like this awesome plane.
丹 你有什么成果了吗
Dan, do you have any results yet?
哦 我现在一天给这些灵长动物注射两次
Oh, well, I've been injecting the primates twice a day.
I-13开智药物 我希望一周以后
with the I-13 intelligence drug. I'm hoping in a week or so…
我希望在凯撒身上投入的时间和资金
I hope Caesar is not just.
能有所回报
a big waste of time and money.
我要向董事会汇报的
I'm the one responsible to the board.
你能给出一个值得期待的前景吗
Just show me one thing positive.
看 他们还在投粪
Look. They still throw their shit.
至少现在它们开始计分了
But now they can keep score.
我们要加快进度了 什么时候能人体试验
We have to kick-start this thing. When can we go to human trials?
快了 但是有一个中间点
We're close, but there's an intermediate step.
如果I-13在这些主妇身上起效
If the I-13 works on these reality wives…
你最好去检查下脑子
You better check that shit.
切 谁敢检查我
Who gonna check me, boo?
我们居然把研究所的未来
We're pinning the future.
系在未开化的野兽身上
of our lab on wild beasts.
它们不是野兽
They're not beasts.
它们能感知 有自己的家庭
They have feelings, they have families.
雄性站着嘘嘘 雌性蹲着嘘嘘
Males pee standing up, females pee sitting down.
这些猿和你一样
These apes are just like you.
也和我一样 你和我 白人和黑人
And me… you and me, blacks and whites.
当然 更像白人 我们像是白一点的猿人
More like whites, of course. We whites are a lighter shade of ape.
而你则是个黑 嘿 我们都有得膀胱炎的风险
whereas you are bla… dder infection, we're all at risk.
我们刚刚才讨论什么来着 木耳
So, what were we talking about again? Vaginas.
- 闭嘴 - 好的
- Shut up. - Yes, of course.
凯撒必须在董事会上展示些智能
Caesar has got to show some human intelligence at that board meeting…
凯撒恐怕比半数董事都聪明
Caesar's probably smarter than half of those board members.
- 丹 - 我知道你要说什么
- Dan… - I know what you're going to say.
它要是真的那么聪明
"If he's so smart,
怎么还会沦落到被关在笼子里
why is he in a cage?"
被关在笼子里的是你
You're in the cage.
有何贵干
What?
- 哦 你是要这个吗 - 嗯
- Oh, you're looking for this? - Uh-huh.
那是我的芭蕾娃娃
It's my ballerina doll.
- 你自己做的 - 麻麻做的
- You made this? - Mama did,
把小木枝 苔藓 蜘蛛网 麻雀骨 蜥蜴眼
using twigs, moss, spiderwebs, sparrow bones, lizard eyes,
- 用耗子口水黏合 - 哦 恶心
- all held together with rat droppings. - Oh, geez.
啊 啊 啊 你在做什么
Ah, ah, ah. What… what are you doing?
我实在没法面对那些孩子 他们太诡异了
I just can't deal with these kids. They're creepy.
我们不该带他们回来的
We should just take 'em back.
也许你们需要找点共同话题
Maybe you guys just need to find some common ground.
比如凯西不离身的芭蕾娃娃
What about that ballerina doll Kathy's always playing with?
我不想提芭蕾这档事
I don't want to talk about the ballet.
我永远忘不了芭蕾对我妈妈的影响
I saw what the ballet did to my mom.
她太如痴如醉了
She became obsessed.
甚至在怀着我的时候还参加天鹅湖的演出
She even danced the swan while she was pregnant with me.
油 油
Boo, ray, boo! Shh!
嘘什么嘘 你个小兔崽子
Shh. Hell. You better sit back.
最好在喉咙被揍断前乖乖坐好
before I punch you in your damn throat.
老娘这在看戏呢
We're trying to enjoy the show.
你小子再敢在那边嘘 嘘 小心我削你
You go on… shh… shh me again. I double-dog dare you, hell.
也不打听打听老娘是谁
Better ask somebody who I am.
哦
Whoa!
传得好
Got it.
妈妈再也没能恢复
Mom was never the same.
这种事会发生纯属上帝脑子抽了
That's unlikely to ever happen again, ever.
就听我一次呗 看看这个
Just give it a shot. Look what I found earlier.
我知道这只是个小制作
I mean, I know it's just a local production.
但也能成为你和凯西的一点谈资
But could be something for you and Kathy to talk about, could be fun.
- 你真这么想 - 对啊
- You really think so? - Yes.
好吧 那我就去瞅瞅
Well, I suppose I could check it out.
好啦 但是一遇到障碍 我就要放弃的哦
OK. But the minute it becomes too difficult, I'm giving up.
就是这种精神
That's the spirit.
虽然朱迪回归芭蕾的初衷
Even though Jody only returned to the ballet.
只是为了亲近女儿
to connect with the girls,
但是想要成为天鹅皇后的欲望
as she got closer she couldn't help but get excited at the prospect.
愈来愈强烈
of becoming the Swan Queen.
本季我们用天鹅湖开场
This season we open with "Swan Lake."
众所周知 这个选段有着芭蕾舞中
As you all know, this piece has the most challenging.
最具有挑战性的角色 天鹅女王
and demanding role in all of ballet… the Swan Queen.
瞄到了不少重量级竞争对手
Sizing up her competition,
朱迪已经能闻到腥风血雨的味道
Jody knew the battle would be a tough one.
白天鹅和黑天鹅
The white and the black.
幸运的是我们有海瑟·达尔西的加盟
Fortunately we have with us prima ballerina and the lead.
她是我们的首席芭蕾舞演员
in my last 146 productions…
和我之前所有演出的领舞
Heather Darcy.
啊 经验丰富的专业人士
Ah, the seasoned professional.
聪明 执拗 上了年纪 饱经风霜
The still brilliant, crusty, old, weathered,
有着魔鬼脸庞的芭蕾前辈和这些
leather-faced elder statesman of ballet to whom these young girls,
没经验 美丽诱人
less experienced, more beautiful and delicious,
但是仍然太嫩了的年轻姑娘们
but still very raw ballerina hopefuls, look up.
给这些迷人的孩子们露一手吧
Show these far more desirable children how it's done, huh?
音乐起
Music!
展示下那招 跳跃后
Try that thing where you are skipping.
单脚跳再岔开双腿
and you hop and you spread your legs a little bit.
看看那派头 那技巧
Look at that form, that technique.
我拍马都追不上
I'll never be that good.
对了 我叫朱迪
I'm Jody, by the way.
坎德拉
Kendra.
- 你也要试试吗 - 我
- Are you going to try out? - Me?
哦 我不知道 我喜欢跳舞 但是
Oh, I don't know. I mean, I like to dance, but I just…
我不喜欢成为视线的焦点
I don't like to be the center of attention.
- 下一个 - 哦 好吃的
- OK, who's next? - Oh, food.
呃
Huh?
我感觉我第一次见识到了芭蕾的真谛
It is as if I am seeing ballet for the first time.
这算哪门子芭蕾
That's not ballet.
这种激情 这种感官享受
The passion, the sensuality.
这个臀部让人想钻进去然后一辈子不出来
An ass that makes you want to crawl inside and take up residence.
我也能跳得有激情
I can show passion.
噢耶
Oh, yeah.
噢耶 噢耶
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh.
朱迪确实很努力
Jody certainly had her work cut out for her.
但坎德拉那个小妞简直性感到爆了
That Kendra chick was smokin'.
你收欧元吗
Do you accept euros?
凯西 莉莉 艾丹
Kathy, Lily, Aidan?
- 朱迪 - 啊
- Jody? - Ah!
哦 亲爱的 太对不起了
Oh, sweetie, I'm so sorry.
- 对不起 - 我没事
- I'm so sorry. - I'm fine.
锅竟然在地板上
It was on the floor.
可能是螺丝松了 我会修的
Ah, probably a screw loose. I'll fix it.
我感觉房间里有什么东西
I feel like there's something in this house.
有什么
Like what?
我感觉脖子后有一股暖湿腐烂的气息
Like I feel hot, clammy, foul-smelling breath on my neck.
你需要给灵媒打电话 驱驱鬼
You need call psychic. Kill bad spirits.
- 哦 - 不 玛利亚 别再来这一套了
- Ugh. - No, Maria, enough of this stuff.
好吧 我来祷告 我来保护这个家
OK, then I do blessing, I protect house.
亲爱的 放松点
Honey, you really need to relax.
你只是带孩子累着了
You're just stressed out about the children.
不 是这个房子的问题 我能感觉到
No, it's this house. I… I feel it.
还有玛利亚不太正常 说实话 你相信她吗
And Maria's a little off. I mean, honestly do you really trust her?
亲爱的 不别担心 她连一个苍蝇都不忍心杀
Oh, honey, don't worry, she couldn't hurt a fly.
你明天还有正事要做呢
Look, you have a big day ahead of you tomorrow.
咱们赶紧休息吧 好吗
Let's just get you some sleep, OK?
爱你
Love you.
我不敢相信 我们的房子竟然被抢了
I don't believe this… our whole house ransacked.
你没关门就走了 家里也没人看着
You leave the house unattended with the doors unlocked.
你看看家都什么样了
and look what happens.
什么也没丢 只是有人故意捣乱
They didn't take anything. It's just vandalism.
除了孩子们的房间没事 其他的都被祸害了
Every room except the kids' rooms was trashed.
这么说你觉得是孩子们干的
So you suspect the kids?
是麻麻 麻麻干的
It was Mama. Mama did it.
她恨这个房子 她恨你们
She hates this house. She hates you.
玛利亚 这是摄像机 必要的全天录像
OK, Maria, this is camera. Necesito filming.
谢谢你帮我收拾 亲爱的
Thank you for helping me clean up, sweetie.
哦 嘿 我找这个找了一大圈
Oh, hey, been looking all over for this thing.
我可是威风不减当年啊
Still got it…
对不起 天啊 救命啊 亲爱的
I'm sorry! God, help, honey!
玛利亚 亲爱的 救命啊
Maria, honey, help!
天啊 玛利亚 把摄像机
Geez! Maria, put the camera…
看这个
Oh, look at this.
我小的时候我妈训练我的样子
Mom coaching me when I was a little girl.
她总是实施内疚策略
Aw… Always applying the guilt trip.
这让我得到了领舞
That got me the lead.
看 玛利亚
Look, Maria.
玛利亚 看我找到了什么 这是啥呀
Maria, look what I found. What is this?
哦 那 那是个新型的电动牙刷
Oh, uh, that's… a new type of electric toothbrush.
震动能把你的牙垢除掉
Vibrations knock the tartar off your teeth.
- 看 这有一大盒子的电动牙刷 - 哇哦
- Look, a whole box of toothbrushes. - Whoa.
- 这个黑色的好大啊 - 行了
- This black one is huge. - OK.
- 看 这还有个两头的 - 知道了
- And look, here's a double-sided one. - All right.
那个还能绑在我脑袋上
And one that I can strap on to my face.
不能 放这边来
Nope. Put that over here.
丹叔叔 这是什么 带珠子的牙线吗
Uncle Dan, what is this? Beaded floss?
那是个成年人用的牙线 亲爱的
That's grown-up floss, honey.
还给我涂鸦
Graffiti!
你看见了吗
Did you see this?
谁画的 我们怎么 玛利亚
Who does that? What are we… Maria.
玛利亚 拜托
Maria, por favor.
朱迪小姐 朱迪小姐
Miss Jody, Miss Jody,
你给这个人打电话 布莱恩先生
you call this man… Mr. Blaine.
他帮了我的妹妹
He helped my sister.
- 这是个灵媒 - 对 他会帮你的
- This is a psychic. - Si, he'll help you.
不 我们真正需要的是更多的安保摄像头
No, what we really need are more security cameras.
丹叔叔 你知道吗
Uncle Dan. You know,
这些牙刷长的可真像假阳具啊
these toothbrushes look an awful lot like dildos.
哦
Ow!
真好玩 麻麻
This is fun, Mama.
你们还没睡啊
You're still awake?
行了 听着 丹叔叔出院前
All right, listen, guys, it's just us.
就我们几个在一起了
until Uncle Dan comes back from the hospital.
我不喜欢这样 你们也不喜欢
I don't like it, you don't like it,
尤其是我不喜欢
I don't like it.
现在去睡觉 我明天还要起早练芭蕾呢
Now go to sleep. I have to be up early for ballet tomorrow.
你真的很喜欢芭蕾是吧
You really like ballet, don't you?
嗯 但我不想让你去
Yeah, but I don't want you to go.
为什么
Why?
麻麻说你会出意外的
Mama says you're going to have an accident.
哦 好吧 是那个祸害了房子的麻麻说的吗
Oh, OK. Is this the same Mama who trashed the house?
本质上说 是的
Basically, yes.
别进去
Don't go in there.
我没打算进去
I wasn't going to.
千万别进去
Just don't.
这是我的房子 我想进就进
It's my house, I can if I want.
我要是你我就不进去
I wouldn't.
- 就进 - 不许进
- Would. - Wouldn't.
- Would, too. - Would not.
你猜怎么着 我才是成年人 你命令不了我
You know what? I'm the adult. You're not the boss of me.
别进
Don't.
我叫你别让人进来
I told you not to let anyone in!
于是朱迪就
And so Jody was…
哦 我的天啊 我能闻到那个味
Oh, my God, I just smelled that.
熏死我了 我的妈呀
It just got to me, yeah.
于是朱迪就
And so Jody was…
哦 受不了了 对不起 失陪一下
Oh, no, I… I'm sorry, you have to excuse me.
我得呼吸点新鲜空气
I got to get some fresh air.
下一节你们自己看吧
The next section should explain itself.
好 注意了
All right, attention.
我一句话不重复第二遍
I do not wish to repeat myself.
我重复一遍 我一句话不重复第二遍
I repeat, I do not wish to repeat myself.
给我戴上那个像个围巾一样的毛衣
I require the sweater I wear as a scarf.
啊 真舒服 嗯
Ah. Comfortable, huh?
妈 别这样 我在工作
Mm… Mother, please, I am working.
好 因为海瑟·达尔西太老了
All right, because Heather Darcy is so old, this season.
这一季我们需要选一个新的天鹅皇后
we will have a new Swan Queen,
这个人就是朱迪·桑德斯
and that person is Jody Sanders.
现在 朱迪给大家展示一下你的才能
Now, Jody, show us your routine.
不 我是天鹅皇后
No, I'm the Swan Queen.
看我的 啊
Watch me. Ah!
我刚说了 我选择的新
As I was saying, my choice for new…
她 是谁都不能是她
Her?! Anyone but her!
你还不如选那个扫地的
You might just as well have picked the janitor!
我吗
Me?
- 艾拉 别闹了 - 什么
- Ira, please, not now. OK. - What?
是 这是个艰难的选择
Yes, it was a difficult decision,
但我一直很喜欢朱迪
but I have always been attracted to Jody.
我怎么能不喜欢她呢
How could I not?
她有着五年级小男孩的身体
She has the body of a fifth-grade boy.
但是 如果她一旦不能演出
But in the event that she is unable to dance,
我任命坎德拉·布鲁克斯作为替补演员
I am naming as her understudy Kendra Brooks.
行了 该吃午饭了
All right, that's lunch.
哦 房子真不错 我去找女孩玩
Ooh, this is a nice house. I'm gonna go find the girls.
凯西 你是怎么知道我今天跳芭蕾会出意外的
Kathy, how did you know I was going to have an accident today at the ballet?
麻麻告诉我的
Mama told me.
好吧 那麻麻是怎么知道我会出意外的
OK, well, how did Mama know I was going to have an accident?
哦 你在这啊 我在头上找到了一个绷带
Oh, there you are. I found this bandage on my head.
丹 别闹 我觉得这个房子里有蹊跷
Dan, please. I think there is something going on in this house,
有个叫麻麻的东西
something about this Mama.
我要给玛利亚告诉我们的那个灵媒打电话
I'm gonna call the psychic Maria told us about.
朱迪 你真的觉得我们需要灵媒吗
Jody, do you really think we need a psychic?
丹叔叔 过来
Uncle Dan, come here.
- 来了 - 我要给你看些东西
- Coming. - I want to show you something.
丹叔叔 麻麻教了我一些小把戏 看我的
Uncle Dan, Mama taught me some tricks. Look what I can do.
- 哦 真厉害 亲爱的 - 爸爸
- Oh, wow, that's really good, honey. - Dada.
阿爹你个娘咧
Good Lord.
- 丹叔叔 看我 - 恶魔
- Uncle Dan, look at me. - Evil spirits.
看 丹先生 看
Look, Mr. Dan, look.
那个不是朱迪的泳衣吗
Isn't that one of Jody's bathing suits?
你正面对着人类无法想象的事情
You're facing something our human minds cannot imagine.
麻麻
Mama.
咱们还是给你找个浴袍穿上吧
Let's get you in a robe.
你想知道我今天芭蕾练得怎么样吗
Do you want to hear about the ballet today?
麻麻在帮我们准备
Mama's helping us get ready.
哦 好 那我也刷牙
Oh, OK, I'll brush, too.
咦 我的牙刷去哪了
Hm. Where did my toothbrush go?
嘿 不许舔自己的蛋蛋
Hey, we don't lick our balls in this house.
抱歉 不会再有下次了
Sorry, won't happen again.
不管朱迪怎么努力
Try as she might,
她都无法和孩子们交心
Jody just couldn't seem to connect with those kids.
也无法除掉她嘴里那个牙刷的味道
Or get the taste of that toothbrush out of her mouth.
只是八岁儿童的青春期焦虑在作怪吗
Was it just eight-year-old teen angst,
还是有其他世界的力量在煽风点火
or were there otherworldly forces at work here?
- 宝贝 - 啊
- Baby. - Hm?
- 宝贝 我听见一些声音 - 什么声
- Babe, I heard something. - What?
我感觉厨房有人
I think there's someone in the kitchen.
你看 根本没人
See? There's nobody down here.
又来了 就在那 去看看
There it is again! Right there. Go look.
朱迪 冷静点 看 没什么可担心的 只是
Jody, calm down. See, there's nothing to worry about. It's just…
哦 天啊 我去
Oh, God! Geez!
丹 我给那个灵媒打电话了
Dan, I'm calling the psychic!
啊 打吧
Ah! Make the call!
布莱恩·福尔达 专业灵媒
Blaine Fulda, professional psychic.
你好 我是朱迪
Hi, I'm Jody.
- 是 你好 - 这是我的丈夫丹
- Indeed you are. - Yes. And this is my husband Dan.
按你的要求 酬劳是500美金的匿名汇票
Your payment as requested. $500 in unmarked bills.
当然 你认识玛利亚吧
And of course, you know Maria.
你好啊 布莱恩先生
Hola, Mr. Blaine.
你好 玛利亚 你妹妹还好吗
Hi, Maria. How's your sister?
死了 恶魔杀了她
Dead. Demon kill her.
好吧 怪不得打电话没人接
Well, that explains the unreturned phone calls.
我感受到了邪恶的气息
I'm sensing evil.
我得拿一些你们的私人物品
I'm gonna have to get some of your personal belongings here,
检查一下不散的恶魔和鬼魂
just so I can check for demon and ghost residue.
我一个人抬不了那么多监视器
I'm not gonna be able to lift all those monitors,
但明天我会让我表弟开白色货车过来
but I'll send my cousin tomorrow with the white van.
他能把监视器都放进去
He can get them in there.
昨晚丹被厨房给袭击了
Dan was attacked by the kitchen last night.
我们觉得可能是麻麻干的
We think it might be Mama.
厨房袭击人
Kitchen attack?
你该早点说
You could've said that earlier.
如果房间找你的麻烦 那不是鬼魂就是恶魔
If a room turns on you, it's either a ghost or a demon.
恶魔可以操控人吗 比如说 活在他们体内
Can a demon take over someone? Like, live within them?
靠 挺瘆人啊
Damn, that's some scary shit.
所以恶魔是最糟糕的情况吗
So a demon is about the worst thing you can have?
不 夫人 性病是最糟糕的情况
No, ma'am, an STD is the worst thing that you can have.
你知道有谁想伤害你们吗
Who do you know who wants to hurt you?
有没有妒忌你的同事
Do you have a jealous colleague at work?
或者是被你忽略的脸书朋友
A Facebook friend you might have ignored?
也许你领养了一个名叫
Maybe you adopted a small African child.
伊卡塔巴布韦的非洲小孩
named Ikatababwe,
答应了每天给这个黑鬼二十五美分的食物
promising to feed this nigga for 25 cents a day.
但他也需要喝水啊
But then he needs something to drink!
- 总之 咱们开始吧 - 好吧
- Anyway, let's begin. - OK.
这是一个魔鬼交流器
This is the evil communicator.
带上它 我就能进入另一个次元
When I put this on, I'll be able to cross over to the other side.
跟邪恶的一方对峙 这会立即引发
and confront the entity. That will immediately trigger.
最后的350美元费用
the final $350 payment of.
用于迪莎·福尔达的抚养费
child support to Tisha Fulda.
请你们手握手 闭上眼 集中思想
And if you guys would just join hands, close eyes and concentrate.
驱散心中的烦恼
Empty your mind of all the thoughts of today's troubles.
将所有一切都抛诸脑后
Everything that went on, get that out of your mind.
专注于精神世界
is all about the spirit world here.
三 二 一
And three, two and one.
这是怎么了 这些东西自己动起来了
What's happening? Things are starting to move all by itself!
呼吸 呼吸
Breathe! Breathe!
等等 我觉着他没法呼吸呀
Wait, I don't think he can breathe!
他是专业的
He's a pro!
拥有这么一套精细复杂的装备
A sophisticated piece of equipment like that?
他当然可以呼吸了
Of course he can breathe.
我靠 我没法呼吸了
Shit, I couldn't breathe.
差点害死自己了 好啦 我沟通过了
Almost killed myself. All right, I communicated.
- 这绝对有一个恶魔 - 额滴神啊
- It was definitely a demon. - Oh, my God.
等一下 我错了 这是个幽灵
Wait a minute. I was wrong. It's a ghost.
力量非常强大
So strong.
哎哟
Ow!
救我 他缠上我了 丹
Help, it's got me! Dan!
丹 醒醒
Dan, wake up!
太太 你快离开这 这是个魔鬼
Ma'am, you got to get out of here. It's evil!
十足的魔鬼 她叫麻麻
It's pure evil! It's Mama!
现在你相信这里有些不对劲了吧
Now do you believe that something's going on?
他被拖走了 嘴里还叫着「麻麻」
He got dragged away, yelling out, "Mama."
他被拖走了吗 我不记得了
He got dragged away? I don't remember that.
- 丹你当时昏过去了 - 这我也不记得了
- Dan, you were unconscious. - I don't remember that, either.
听着 亲爱的 我不是想吵架
Look, honey, I don't want to argue.
重点是我们彼此相爱 对吧
The important thing is, we love each other, OK?
不 重点是可能真的有麻麻这个幽灵
No, the important thing is that this Mama thing could be real.
而且她还想杀掉我们
and she might be trying to kill us.
小朱 那家伙是个骗子 仅此而已 好嘛
Jod, that guy was a fraud and that's it. OK?
- 那是什么 - 我的鸡鸡
- What's that? - My penis.
- 不是的 - 就是的
- No. - Yes.
对 就在那儿 对
There, right now, there.
我懂的 在努力呢
I know. I'm trying.
- 那到底是什么 - 我的鸡鸡
- What the hell is that? - My penis?
那是什么声音
What's making that sound?
丹那是什么
Dan, what is that?
我的鸡鸡
MY penis.
有烟味
Is that smoke?
玛利亚你在干嘛 你会把房子烧掉的
Maria! What are you doing?! You're gonna burn down the house!
我在杀恶灵
Kill bad spirits!
- 怎么了这是 - 玛利亚差点把房子烧了
- What is going on? - Maria almost burned the house down.
- 神马 - 的确如此 她有点
- What? - That's it, she's got…
够了 这全都失控了 你把大家都吓到了
Enough! This is getting out of hand. You're scaring everybody.
你不能解雇她 她陪伴我们很多年了
You can't fire her. I mean, she's been with us for years.
我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do.
- 你这是歧视 - 好吧 这又是神马玩意
- That's discrimination. - OK, now what the hell?
- 这太扯了 - 这是她的信仰 亲爱的
- This is completely insane! - It's what she believes in, honey!
把这给我
Give me that!
你要赶我走啊 你家不安全
You're gonna let me go?! Your family is not safe!
对不起玛利亚 这样下去是不行的
I'm sorry, Maria, it's just not working out.
我的建议是别带孩子了
I'll give you a recommendation, just nothing involving kids.
或者住在靠我们一英里的地方
or within a mile of anyone's house.
我不能在这样了 我得去工作
I can't do this anymore. I got to go to work.
我不懂你在说什么东西
I don't even understand what you're saying!
哦
Ow!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
在过去两年 我们的丹·桑德斯
for the past two years, our own Dan Sanders has been.
在三十只猿猴上测试I-13药剂
testing the I-13 compound on 30 apes.
不幸的是 其中二十九变成了
Unfortunately, 29 of them turned into.
精神错乱暴躁易怒的变态性捕食者
insane, aggressive, deviant sexual predators.
但是只有凯撒
But one, Caesar,
在智力方面有了长足的进步
has experienced a huge leap in intelligence.
他正同时应对三个对手
Here he plays three opponents.
当然对手都是猿猴
Of course, they're apes.
但凯撒的超凡能力归功于一个人
But Caesar's superior capabilities are the work of one man.
那就是I-13项目的研发人 丹·桑…
The brains behind the I-13 project, Dan San…
- 你还好吧 - 我没事 马丁
- Are you OK? - I'm fine, Martin.
女士们先生们 请允许我向你们介绍凯撒
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to introduce you to Caesar…
你甩不掉我的
You're not getting away from me!
喔
Oof!
哦 不
Oh, no!
百老汇街大的交通处于停滞状态
Traffic is backed up on the Broad Street Bridge,
警方在那里和一群猿猴进行枪战
where apparently police are battling dozens of apes in a running gunfight.
据报道 一家实验室的一位科学家
Our reports indicate that a scientist at a research laboratory.
给这些猿猴服用了实验性的开智药物
gave these apes an experimental intelligence drug.
所有警务人员都赶到了现场
I'm being told that all available officers are now on the scene.
但此时我们建议所有观众绕道而行
But at this time, we are advising all our viewers to find alternate routes.
我刚得知我们有一通求救电话
I'm now being told we have the actual 911 call.
提醒了警方情势的严重性
that first alerted the police to the situation.
这里是911 你遇到了什么问题
911, what's your emergency?
天哪 猿猴闯进房子里了
Oh, my God! Apes are inside the house!
冷静 女士 发生了什么
Calm down, ma'am. What happened?
我们当时正在做爱 哦天
We were making love and… Oh, my God!
- 他们在攻击他 - 在攻击谁 女士
- They're attacking him! - Who are they attacking, ma'am?
卡尔 天哪 快救救他
Carl! Oh, my God! Please, help him!
- 你老公在哪里 - 卡尔不是我老公
- Where is your husband right now? - Carl's not my husband.
我老公是十二频道新闻节目主持人
My husband's the anchor for Channel 12 News.
他不能知道这事
He can't know about it.
- 好吧 女士 但我们需要 - 快点
- OK, ma'am, but we need to… - Hurry!
趁我丈夫还在录节目快派人来支援
Send help while my husband's still on the air!
女士 这不重要 重要的是你的生活
Ma'am, that's not important. Your life is.
恩 你说得对 他干嘛在意
Yeah, you're right. Why should he care?
我是说 我敢肯定他和搭档的那个小贱人睡过
I mean, I'm pretty sure he's been sleeping with his co-anchor, that bitch!
我要把她撕个粉…
Oh, I'm gonna rip her…
（啊哦 技术故障请 请不要走开）
恭喜你 姑娘
Congratulations, girl.
我就知道是你 你如此完美 呆板
I knew it was gonna be you. You're just so perfect, so mechanical.
看你跳舞就像看机器人跳舞
Watching you dance is like watching a robot.
谢谢
Thanks.
饿死了
So hungry.
只有这么多啊
Is that all?
皮埃尔有体重限制要求
Pierre has a weight limit.
我太胖了 你看玛拉
I'm too heavy. Look at Mara.
她看起来多棒
She looks great.
你确定你还好吗
Look, are you sure you're OK?
家里发生了奇怪的事情
Weird things have been happening at home.
凯西说会有意外发生
Kathy said there was going to be an accident.
- 然后海瑟就发生了意外 - 这很严重的
- Then it happened to Heather. - That's some serious shit.
你应该和孩子们谈谈
You should talk to those kids.
哇 是比萨耶
Whoa, pizza.
我不停的吃可就是不长胖
I eat and eat and eat, and I don't gain a pound.
海瑟
Heather!
你以为可以取代我
You think you can replace me?
好啊 那我们等着看天鹅怎么吞噬你
Well, we'll see how you like it once the swan consumes you!
我靠
Damn it!
破门
Door!
妈了个巴子
Son of a bitch!
我都不知道原来你这么会搭东西
Oh, I didn't know you were such a good builder.
哇
Wow.
凯西 我希望你告诉我关于麻麻的事
Kathy, I want you to tell me about Mama.
麻麻不喜欢别人谈论她
Mama doesn't like it when you talk about her.
她是谁
Who is Mama?
她是邪恶之书里读过的一个女人
She was a woman who read from an evil book.
有时候她会进入我们的梦里
Sometimes she comes to us in a dream.
在梦里
In a dream?
对 当然在梦里
In your dreams, of course.
真希望我能知晓你的梦境
I wish I could see what's inside your dreams.
来提取你的梦 来个盗梦空间
To extract what's in your dreams. To perform an inception.
能不能别动它 这个大号是我出生的时候吹的
Will you drop that? That's my birth tuba.
你好 我是多姆·寇伯 你要入梦吗
Hello. I'm Dom Kolb. You called about a dream extraction?
对 我要找一本邪恶之术
Yes. I need to find out about an evil book.
这个机器可以让我们进入梦境
This machine will allow us access to the dream world.
开始吧
Let's begin.
那我们什么时候开始做梦
So when do we start dreaming?
你不会记得梦的开始的
You never really remember the beginning of a dream,
- 对吧 - 是吧
- do you? - I guess.
好啦
OK, then,
这是你在共享梦境里的第一课 保持冷静
this is your first lesson in shared dreaming. Stay calm.
对不起 我把手机丢这了
Sorry. I dropped my phone in there.
你要清除所有的潜意识 注意你所想的
You need to clear your subconscious. And watch what you think about.
- 不要太疯狂 - 好的
- Nothing crazy. - Right.
比如你胯下着火了
Like having your crotch burst into flames.
这和麻麻有什么关…
What does that have to do with Ma…
- 喂 - 哦
- Hey! - Oh.
重新来过
Let's start over.
我是朱迪·桑德斯
I'm Jody Sanders.
恩 亲爱的 我正在等你
Yes, my dear. I've been expecting you.
请进
Please, come in.
他们都叫我克里斯蒂安·格雷
They call me Christian Grey.
喜欢我蓝色的房间吗
How do you like my blue room?
- 这是红的 - 哦 我是色盲
- It's red. - Oh. I'm color-blind.
我的装潢师答应过我 算了
My decorator assured me that… Never mind.
喝香槟吗
Champagne?
坐吧
Have a seat.
我站着就行
I'll stand.
嘿 克里斯蒂安 天啊 伙计
Hey, Christian, man, golly, man!
我要好好谢谢你
I'd like to thank you a lot, man,
让我趴在那里就像个吊球一样
for working on my prostrate like it was a speed bag.
的确 迈克尔我得承认我对你的表现也很惊讶
Yes, Michael, I must admit, I was surprised at your performance, as well.
对于一个过气超重脸上纹身的人来说不错了
Not bad for a washed-up, overweight, facially tattooed…
再来一次试试
Do it again.
哦
Oh!
我完全不知道这是什么
I have no idea what that one was.
我也是
Me neither.
麻麻 你在这吗
Mama, are you here?
- 多姆 是你吗 - 天哪
- Dom, is that you? - Oh, shit.
你说过梦想我们一起慢慢变老
You said you'd had a dream that we'd grow old together.
是的 我们会的
Right. And we will.
- 你在这干嘛 - 你好啊
- What are you doing here? - Hi.
你怎么能带她来这 我们的孩子怎么办
How could you bring her here? What about our children?
- 他们是不存在 - 不 他们是的 看
- They're not real. - Yes, they are. Watch.
詹姆斯，裴丽帕
James, Phillippa!
你不会要跳吧
You're not gonna jump, are you?
我怎么没想到 谢谢
I hadn't thought about that. Thank you.
我们一点进展也没有
OK, we're not getting anywhere.
这些和凯西有毛线关系啊
What does any of this have to do with Kathy?
凯西 我以为你就是凯西
Kathy? I thought you were Kathy.
哦
Oh.
葵花点穴手
"Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto."
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?!
- 那肯定是她 - 麻麻
- That must have been her. - Mama.
她想带我们回悬崖
She wants to take us home to the cliff.
- 这是什么意思 - 我不知道
- What does that mean? - I don't know.
但我想你会给我好评的吧
But I trust you'll give me a favorable Yelp review?
朱迪的任务很明确了
Jody's mission was clear.
创造出麻麻的邪恶之书
The evil book that created Mama.
在森林里一个木屋的地下室
was located in the cellar of a cabin, in the woods.
如果她能找到那个木屋 她就能知道答案
If she could find that cabin, maybe she could find some answers.
如果我们能找到那个木屋 我们就能知道答案
If we can find that cabin, maybe we can find some answers.
好吧 淡定 我来看看
OK, calm down. I'm gonna come over.
- 坎德拉 - 干嘛
- Kendra? - What?
等等 到底怎么了
OK, wait, what's going on now?
我觉得她就在楼下
I think she's out there!
别急别急 淡定
OK, OK, just… you stay calm!
前门打开
Front door open.
- 她进来了 - 前门打开
- She's in the house! - Front door open.
- 镇定… - 前门已开
- OK, stay… - Front door open.
你他妈的给我关掉
Shut the hell up!
不需要 贱人
No need for that, bitch.
- 贱人 - 前门打开
- Bitch?! - Front door open.
- 你居然敢叫我贱人 - 前门打开
- No, you did not just call me a bitch! - Front door open…
- 亲爱的 - 丹
- Honey? - Dan?!
抱歉 我不知道是你
I am so sorry. I didn't know who you were and…
没关系 亲爱的 只是巧合 对吧 凯撒
It's OK, honey, it was an accident. Right, Caesar?
当然他可以留在这儿
And of course he can stay here.
看看 凯撒想帮忙做点事
Look at that. Caesar wants to help out around the house.
噢
Aw.
嗨
Hey…
很抱歉 只是我突然看见只大猩猩
I'm sorry, I see an ape,
这是本能反应
I come out swinging.
可以理解
That's understandable.
拿去吧
Here you go.
我很开心看到你没事 但今晚就是个警示
I am so glad you're OK, but tonight was a wake-up call.
我觉得我们找到了那间小屋 好吧
I think we've got to find that cabin.
我想到了一个办法
OK. I got an idea.
等等 我们炒了玛利亚 谁来照顾孩子
Wait, we fired Maria. Who's gonna watch the kids?
我已经搞定了
I already took care of it.
- 淘气保姆来啦 - 见到你很开心 淘气
- Naughty Nanny's here. - Nice to meet you, Naughty.
这是我的妻子朱迪
This is my wife Jody.
3P呀 那可要额外收费哦
Threesome? That costs extra.
天呐 还有只猴子
Oh, Jesus. Monkey, too?
你们都是些什么怪人啊
Oh, you people are freaks,
不过另付一百美元就好
but for an extra $100.
你是叫了哪家机构
What agency did you call?
他们提供护士 拉拉队 还有保姆
Oh, they have nurses and cheerleaders and nannies.
丹 你叫的这是三陪
Dan, you called an escort service.
这就是我们上次我叫圣诞老人的那家机构
I used the same agency to book a Santa for Christmas.
谁在召唤圣诞老人
Someone called for Santa?
嚯嚯嚯
Ho, ho, ho.
丹 你来照看孩子
Dan, you're watching the kids.
朱迪对小屋感到很害怕
Jody was nervous about what she might find at the cabin,
但有凯撒和闺蜜们当得力助手
but she was comforted by the fact.
她又镇定了下来
that Caesar and the girls were in good hands.
你为谁工作
Who do you work for?
坎德拉 这里可不是我说的那个小屋
Kendra, this isn't the cabin I was talking about.
知道 我只是觉得你该放松放松
I know, I just thought you needed to relax.
来一粒
Take one of these.
呃 算了吧
Um, I don't know.
来吧 只会持续几个小时而已
Oh, come on, they'll only last a couple of hours, tops.
坎德拉 我不需要用毒品来放松
Kendra, I don't need drugs to have fun.
来照张相
Let me take a picture. OK.
哇噢 超级性感
Oh, that's so hot!
耶
Yeah!
耶 骑上来 耶 耶
Yeah, ride it, yeah, yeah!
只要一美元就能让你尖叫不已
A dollar will make me holler,
我是宝贝甜心波波
honey boo boo child.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不经常到市区
I don't always go downtown,
但每次去我都会先喝一杯啤酒
but when I do, I drink a beer first.
我是世界之王 哇噢
I'm the king of the world! Woo! Woo!
我邪恶地硬了
I'm wicked hard!
不介意我进行到底吧
Mind if I play through?
噢 糟了
Ooh, shit!
又来 你这个王八蛋 老娘要把你给载了
Again? You son of a bitch, I'm gonna kill you!
噢 天呐 排练要迟到了
Oh, my God, rehearsal. I'm late.
完了完了完了 死定了
Oh, no, oh, my God, oh, my God. Oh, my God.
你们快住嘴
Stop, stop!
噢 朱迪 谢天谢地你终于来了
Oh, Jody, thank God you're here, girl.
我刚在跳舞 顺便亲他
I was just dancing and kissing him.
因为我不想让再想你迟到的事
'cause I didn't want him to think about you being late.
我才是领舞 只有我可以在这里免费赠送香吻
Well, I'm the dancer, so I'll do the kissing around here.
刚才的感觉太棒了
That was amazing.
我想让你当我孩子的母亲
I want you to have my children.
粑粑 拜托 偶们想和你在一起
But, Papa, please, we want to stay with you.
去车里等 加斯顿
Back in the car, Gaston. Aw…
就她怎么可能让你忘了我
She can't make you forget about me.
我睡过头是因为你今早提前走了
I overslept because you just took off this morning.
- 今早 - 对 你在我这里睡的
- This morning? - Yeah, you slept over.
什么 等等 你是不是做了个和我的
What? Wait a minute, did you have some kind of lezzo dream fantasy.
- 拉拉之梦 - 别装无辜了
- about me? - Don't act like you weren't there.
我们做了些很特别的事
We had something special.
我们昨晚的好几个小时都在做爱
We made love last night for hours.
- 什么 - 你现在是不是打算告诉我
- What? - Oh, and now you're gonna tell me.
泰格·伍兹没来和我翻云覆雨
Tiger Woods didn't come out of my vagina?
朱迪
Jody.
你干嘛
What?!
噢 这就对了
Oh, yeah, yeah.
这就解释了我当时的欲望
Well, that explains the poison ivy.
朱迪
Jody?
- 你在这儿啊 - 坎德拉
- There you are. - Kendra?
门开着所以我就进来了
Oh, the door was open so I let myself in.
没关系 听着 我真的很抱歉
It's OK. Look, I'm so sorry.
我真的以为我们昨晚干嘛了
I really believed something happened between us last night.
整件事一直都是我自己幻想出来的
I must have dreamt the whole thing.
不 我们确实爱爱了
Oh, no, we had sex.
但今早你当众说出来
But this morning at rehearsal, you said…
我不能让他们知道我的私事
I can't have the whole cast knowing my business.
我都成功一半了
I'm already doing half of 'em,
再说 我和皮埃尔 我们也
and besides, me and Pierre… we have this little thing…
等等 那这些是什么
Wait, then, what's this?
不知道 这应该是我离开以后的事
Beats me… must have happened after I left.
- 好爽 - 天啊 你疯了吗
- Oh, yeah! - Girl, you are freaky.
好爽
Oh, yeah.
爽死了 天啊
Oh, yeah, get it. Oh, my God.
妈蛋
Oh, shit!
看吧 我就说她是真的
See, I knew she was real.
好吧 我们来找找小屋在哪里
All right, let's find out where this cabin is.
这他妈是什么
What in the hell?
坏孩子
Bad girl.
这是什么
Oh, what is this?
天啊 这和我梦里的房子一模一样 真的
Oh, my God, it's the same cabin from the dream. Of course.
那等我们找到书了以后怎么办
So, what are we gonna do if we find that book?
不知道 如果是那本把妈妈变成现在这样的书
I don't know, if that's the book that turned Mama into what she is,
说不定就能打破诅咒
maybe it could somehow reverse the curse.
我们快到了
OK, we're almost there.
- 我才不要进去 - 我们必须进去
- Hey, I'm not going in there. - We have to go inside.
那本书是解开我噩梦的关键
The book is the key to the nightmare I'm living.
- 你是谁 - 我是朱迪 这位是坎德拉
- Oh, my gosh, who are you? - I'm Jody and this is Kendra.
我们在找一些很重要的东西
We're looking for something very important.
我们都是 进来吧
We all are. Come on in.
∮ 高山上的呼喊 ∮
∮ Go tell it on the mountain ∮
∮ 翻山越岭 ∮
∮ Over the hills and everywhere… ∮
大家看过来 这是朱迪和坎德拉
Everybody, this is Jody and Kendra.
- 朱迪 坎德拉 你们好 - 你们好
- Hello, Jody and Kendra. - Hi.
抱歉我没法站起来
Pardon me for not standing,
我在处理这只鸟翅膀上的伤口
but I'm mending the wing of this bird that.
我在树林里发现它的
we found in the woods.
好吧 我们很急
OK. Hi, we're in a hurry.
我们在找一本可以救人的书
We're actually looking for a book that could save lives.
- 对 我已经找到了 - 谢天谢地
- Yes, I've got it right here. - Oh, thank God.
确实该感谢他 圣经 让我念给你听
Thank him indeed. The Bible. Here, let me read to you.
不不不 听着 其实我们在找
Oh, no, no, see, we're actually looking for…
- 找一本邪恶之书 - 我很了解恶魔
- …the book of evil. - I know evil all too well.
- 真的吗 - 这周都花在米娅身上了
- You do? - This weekend's devoted to Mia.
降魔周
It's a detox weekend.
她最近迷上了小瓶饮料
She's hooked on energy shots.
那真纠结
Oh, yeah, that's a real struggle.
好了 听着 我们在找另一本书
OK, listen, we're looking for another book.
- 就在这间屋子里 - 我们什么都没看见
- somewhere in this cabin. - Hm. We haven't seen anything.
我们已经尽力了 走吧
We gave it a shot, let's get out of here.
等等
OK, wait.
- 这里有地窖吗 - 得了
- Is there a cellar? - Great.
就在那儿
There it is. Oh!
（千万别看）
（绝对是个坏主意）
我才不管它写着什么
OK, I don't care what it says.
诅咒是由四个单词开始的
"The curse begins with four words.
葵花点穴手
"Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto."
你们今晚都会死去
You're all going to die tonight.
诅咒以一个单词作结
"The curse ends with one word.
解
Adunda."
见鬼
What the heck?
- 发生了什么 - 我成杨过了
- Why? - I don't have an arm.
不滋为森么我把色头切层娘半了
For some reason I cut my tongue in half.
好吧 我们至少把歌唱完吧 大家牵着手
OK, well, let's at least finish the song. Everyone hold hands.
- 埃里克除外 - 该死
- Except for Eric. - Damn.
∮ 高山上的呼喊 ∮
∮ Go tell it on the mountain ∮
∮ 翻山越岭 ∮
∮ Over the hills and everywhere ∮
也许我们的方法不对
Well, maybe we didn't do it right.
葵花点穴手
"Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto."
解
"Adunda."
这次又怎么了 我的手哪儿去了
Why does this keep happening? Where's my arm?
- 仄是你的吗 - 那是左手
- Is this yours? - That's a left.
那是我的 你能把它递给我吗
That's mine. Could you hand it to me, please?
- 我要一只右手 - 埃里克锯掉的
- I need a right. - Eric chainsawed it off.
- 我错了 - 我的 我的腿呢
- Look, I'm sorry. - My… My leg?
不 那条是黑的 不是我的
No, that's black. It's not mine.
- 妈的 - 我都不知道该怎么办了
- Oh, shit. - I don't know what I'm gonna do.
悲伤逆流成河
Oh, cry me a river.
我需要帮助 我想上厕所
I'm gonna need a little help. I have to go to the bathroom.
- 但我的弟弟在那角落里 - 太操蛋了
- My penis is in the corner. - This is fucked up.
我试试
Let me try.
葵花点穴手
"Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto."
还是什么都没有
Nothing again.
知道吗 我们该走了
You know what? Let's go.
等等 那里有扇门
Wait, there's a door right here.
走这边
Let's go out this way.
不错 这样就不用走那些奇怪的楼梯了
OK, cool, we can avoid the weirdos upstairs.
∮ 我们会逮到你 ∮
∮ We're gonna get you ∮
∮ 我们会偷看 ∮
∮ Not another peep ∮
葵花点穴手
Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto. Gort Klaatu Barada Nikto.
在从小屋回家的路上
Kendra and I recited the Latin words over and over.
我和坎德拉一遍又一遍重复着这些拉丁文
at the cabin and on the way home.
我们说了几百遍 还是什么都没发生
We must have said it a hundred times, but nothing happened.
它会不会不是我们要找的那本书
What if it isn't the right book?
或许葵花点穴手已经被锁定了
Maybe the curse has somehow been lifted.
对丹和朱迪来说 幸运的是
Luckily for Dan and Jody, there was someone in the house.
多亏了I-13配方
who, thanks to the I-13 formula,
家里有人的智力和认知能力大大提升
had increased intelligence and superior cognitive ability.
他的问题解决能力让他
His analytical problem-solving skills allowed him…
能够探查出重要信息
…to ascertain crucial information.
这是一个现代科学的奇迹
A marvel of modern-day science,
他的智商甚至超过了
his IQ had surpassed even the most…
噢 该死
Aw, hell.
我为什么会觉得你有智力
Why did I think you could be intelligent?
你就是个蠢猩猩
You're nothing but a dumb animal.
嗷
Ow!
蠢货
Idiot!
- 我能讲人话了 - 嗨 凯撒
- I can talk. - Hey, Caesar.
史蒂夫
Steve?
丹家有个恶魔
Dan's got a mad demon in his house.
- 马特·达蒙在他家 - 不是 是个恶魔
- Matt Damon's in his house? - No, a mad demon.
我爱死马特·达蒙 杰森·伯恩
I love Matt Damon. Jason Bourne.
哎
Oy.
我早就该知道不该把这个野猩猩带回家
I should have known not to bring a wild animal into the house.
我 我真的抱歉
I'm… I'm so sorry.
我曾相信凯撒 我以为他与众不同
But I believed in Caesar. I thought he was different.
事情可能没有这么简单
There's something more to this.
- 我能感觉得到 - 不 他就是抽风了
- I can feel it. - No, he just… went crazy.
算了 但是我还是觉得麻麻在这屋里
Forget it. But I still think Mama could be in this house.
- 你不觉得 - 我们花费了一个晚上找些
- But don't you… - We just had a whole night go on.
- 毫无征兆的东西 - 也许吧
- without a single sign of anything. - I guess.
我只是昨晚被孩子们吓到了
I was just so scared last night for the kids.
你要醒醒脑了
You're coming around.
我是喜欢上她们了吗
Am I getting attached to them?
是梦里的那个悬崖
It's the cliff from the dream.
快进车 别逼我骂娘
Get in the car now. Don't make me yell!
我来了 撒旦 我会用这些孩子向您献祭
Unto thee, Satan, I sacrifice these children.
来到悬崖边的老家 完蛋了
Return home to the cliff of… Holy shit!
家就在悬崖 天哪 孩子们
Home is at the cliff. Oh, my God. Girls!
凯西 没事了 我看见悬崖了
Kathy. It's OK. I saw the cliff.
我知道家的意思了
I know what "home" means.
惨了
Whoa!
孩子们快来 我们去接艾丹
Come on, girls. Let's go get Aidan.
酷毙了
That's cool.
莉莉 走了
Lily! Come on.
艾丹 你还好吗
Aidan! Are you OK?
丹叔叔 丹叔叔
Uncle Dan! Uncle Dan!
是麻麻 麻麻 麻麻
Mama! Mama! Mama!
她在这
She's here!
姑娘们别急 一个个来 莉莉 你先说
Whoa. Girls, girls, girls. One at a time. Lily, you first.
明白了 凯西到你了
Got it. Now Kathy.
是麻麻 麻麻 她在这 她要杀了我们
Mama! Mama! She's here! She's gonna kill us!
我得告诉你们多少次这世上没有这种事
How many times do I have to tell everyone there's no such thing as…
玛利亚 你怎么会在这
Maria? What are you doing here?
我很生气你炒了我鱿鱼
I was angry you fire me,
所以我烤了个这个给你
so I bake you this.
屎派
A shit pie?
- 谢谢 但是 - 再来根热狗
- Uh, thanks, but… - Hot dog?
不了 这还是芥末屎味的
No, that's still shit with mustard.
那来跟香蕉 营养操鸡好
Maybe just a banana, then? Very much potassium.
不错吧 丹先生
So bueno, Mr. Dan.
对不起 我应该相信你说的话的
No, I… I'm sorry. I should have listened to you…
丹先生 我们有过过节 但是我是爱你的
Mr. Dan, we have our problems, but I always love you.
很爱很爱
So much.
见到你 就像见到我的父亲
When I see you, I see my father.
丹 丹 我们得
Dan. Dan, we have to…
- 等等 发生了什么 - 我能解释
- Wait. What's going on here? - I can explain.
没时间了 麻麻抓走了孩子
There's no time. Mama has the girls.
我知道她带去哪了
I know where she took them.
该走了
Got to go.
你让我想起了我父亲
You remind me of my father.
丹
Dan!
得知孩子们有危险
Knowing the girls were in danger,
丹和朱迪快马加鞭 往悬崖赶去 他们
Dan and Jody sped off, racing to get to the cliff they…
咦 他们的车呢
Oh, my God. What happened to the car?
去哪了 哦 在这儿
Where? Oh, there it is.
他们不会眼睁睁得看着那女鬼跳下悬崖
They were no longer able to sit idly by and let a ghost jump off a cliff,
- 用他们的孩子殉葬 - 凯西 莉莉
- sacrificing their children with her. - Kathy! Lily!
天哪 她们在那 凯西 莉莉快停下
Oh, my God. There they are. Kathy, Lily, stop!
- 我们该怎么办 - 我只要
- What do we do now? - Um, I'll just…
吟诵这本书上的葵花点穴手换回她的人性
…read from this and change her back to human.
姑娘们快跑 快跑啊 不对
Girls, run! Run! No.
不对 方向错了 往悬崖反方向跑
No, not that way. Away from the cliff!
我不会再让麻麻带走你们的
I'm not going to let Mama take you away again.
嗯
Hm?
莉莉停下 来这嘛 好姑娘 到这来 莉莉
Lily, stop! Come on. Come on. Here, girl. Come on, Lily.
过来 看 什么好东西耶
Come on. Look. Oh, look. Yeah.
来这 瞧瞧这个 莉莉
Come on. Look. Oh, yeah. Lily.
噢耶 哇哦
Oh, wow. Yeah.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
够了 疯够了吧
Enough! This is crazy.
莉莉不是小狗
Lily's not a dog.
她是那个我慢慢喜欢上的小美女
She's a beautiful little girl who I've grown to love.
我爱这些孩子 麻麻 即使他们不都爱我
I love all these children, Mama, even if they don't all love me.
莉莉也爱你 朱迪
Lily loves you, too, Jody.
他们属于我和丹
And they belong in this world with me and Dan.
因为他们值得拥有有血有肉的家长
Because they deserve parents who aren't decomposing.
好孩子
Good girl.
好了 够了
All right, enough.
在哪一页来着 完了 找不到了
Where's the page? Damn it, I can't find it.
算了
Forget it.
走你 看来不行
There, that worked. Maybe not.
兄弟 我们不该再抽这货了
Man, we need to stop smoking this shit.
我就说那条鲨鱼迟早有用
Told you that shark was going to come in handy.
谢谢你 莉莉
Thank you. Lily.
宝贝 谢天谢地你没事
Honey, thank God you're all right.
- 该你上场了 - 坎德拉
- Your cue is coming up. - Oh, Kendra.
听着 没事的 忘了发生过的一切吧
Look, it's OK, girl. Let's forget about what happened.
- 你是黑天鹅 - 不 你才是
- You are the Black Swan. - No. It's you.
把麻麻扔下悬崖后 我重新认识到了孰轻孰重
Throwing Mama off the cliff has really made me reevaluate my priorities.
家庭第一 你来跳黑天鹅吧
My family comes first. You dance the Black Swan.
- 因为有时候我们的人生 - 太好了
- Because sometimes in life… - OK.
下面有请新黑天鹅 坎德拉·布鲁克斯小姐
Introducing our new Swan Queen, Miss Kendra Brooks.
- 这不是芭蕾 - 绝对不是
- This is not ballet. - No, it the hell ain't.
真他么扯淡
This some bullshit.
我就说嘛 对吧对吧
That's what I'm talking about! Right? Right?
你知道的 对吧
You know that shit, right?
我们的故事结束了
And so our story ends.
如果要从中学到什么的话
If anything is to be learned from this,
那就是人类真是个可悲的民族
it's that mankind is a pathetic race.
这个世界需要猩猩来统治
and apes need to take over this planet.
趁你们还在的时候好好享受地球吧
Enjoy Earth while you still got it.
好啊 那我们等着看天鹅怎么吞噬你
Well, we'll see how you like it once the swan consumes you!
我憋不了这么久 太久了
I cannot hold it that long. It's, like… it's so long.
来亲亲
We're kissing.
停停
Cut! Cut!
停
Cut!
夺命连环吻
We're kissing.
停
Cut!
- 怎么了 - 那家伙入镜了
- What happened? - Guy was in the shot.
- 哈哈 - 停
- Ah. - Cut!
他是魔鬼造型吗
But was he dressed like a demon?
把第二个「我的小弟弟」当一个问句来说
Do the second "my penis" as a question.
没问题 那「我的另一个小弟弟」也是这样
OK. And then "my other penis" is a question also?
- 是的 - 好的
- Yeah. - OK.
但是记得你要跳到「什么鬼东西」这句
But remember, you're jumping to "What the hell is that?"
知道了 但是不知道为什么
I know. I don't know why.
对的 你在跳
You're jumping… Yeah.
这么多的小弟弟
There's just so many penises.
欢迎到好莱坞
Welcome to Hollywood.
- 我准备好了 - 嘿
- I'm ready for it. - Hey.
我完全能接受
I'm OK with this.
这是临时的护士淋浴点
That's the temporary nurses' shower.
- 我们正在油漆中 - 停
- And we're painting it. - Cut.
这是 临时护士淋浴点
That's the… temporary nurses' shower.
我能接受这个
I'm OK with this.
对不起 大家 我
Sorry, you guys. I…
我能接受这个
I'm OK with this.
这是护士的临时衣帽间
That's the nurses' temporary locker room,
我们正在重漆它
and we're repainting it.
停
Cut.
哎哟 有人吗
Ouch. Hello here!
B点
B mark!
- 背景准备 - 开拍
- And background. - Action!
天哪
Oh!
朱迪 谢天谢地找到你了
Jody! Thank God I caught you.
我忘了告诉你 现在你是天鹅皇后了
I forgot to tell you, now that you are the Swan Queen…
去你的
Suck my…
我会救你的 史努比
I'll save you, Snoop Dogg.
我的的角色名不是史努比 老兄
My name ain't Snoop Dogg in this… movie, man!
- 我的意思是我 - 嘘
- Well, I mean, I… - Sh…
别搞
Stop it!
我们好着呢
We're good. We're good.
准备好迎接一夜美妙绝伦的激情
Now prepare for a night of unparalleled passion.
等等 格雷先生
Oh, wait, wait, Mr. Grey…
暂停密语是「深入」
The safe word is "deeper."
什么
What?
该死 噢
Damn! Ow!
啊
Whoa!
这些和芭蕾有什么关系
What does all this have to do with the ballet?
- 芭蕾 - 你不是捐了上百万吗
- Ballet? - Yes. Aren't you donating millions?
上百万 搞什么 我都破产了
Millions? What? I'm broke.
我的心血都投入到这件房间了
Every cent I have has been put into this room.
我不知道我该怎么办
I don't know what I'm going to do.
噢 悲伤逆流成河
Oh, cry me a river.
帮个忙吧 我的小弟弟都没了
I'm going to need a little help. I don't have a penis.
脱不下来
It does not come off.
脱都脱不下来 抱歉
It does not come off. I'm sorry.
我真是懒得说这些（哔）
I'm getting tired of talking about this…
和这个家伙在树林里
In the woods with this man.
（哔）家伙 我们一直在兜圈子
…man, we keep going in circles,
谈论一个（哔）家伙
talking about a… man.
来谈谈这个（哔）家伙
Let's talk about a… man,
或者找些（哔） 找些（哔）
or getting some… getting some…
讲（哔）这两个蠢货在树林里
Talking about… these two dudes in the woods.
如果我们能有个（哔）
If we had a… here, she could wash our…
她立马会帮我们洗掉（哔）
off right now.
你懂吗 这就是我想说的
You understand me? That's the way I would say it.
嗨 宝贝 来从这本巫术书里找找线索
Hey, babe, check out this psychic's book for a clue.
- 吓死我了 - 拜托 没什么
- It really freaks me out. - Come on, there's nothing to be…
啊
Nuh!
这些书都是
These books are all…
没什么好害怕的
There's nothing to be scared…
好怕的
…to be scared…
哦 没什么好怕的
Oh, there's nothing to be scared…
哦 翻错动物了
Oh, wrong animal.
好害怕的 一个恐龙
…be scared… A dinosaur?
这其中有什么联系
What does this have to do with…
抱歉
I know. Sorry.
开拍
And… action!
- 这其中有什么联系 - 对不起
- What does this have to do with… - Sorry.
你一直揉咪咪 抱歉没忍住
You just keep cupping your boobs. OK, sorry.
好吧 你怎么知道谁是女巫
OK, how do we know who's a witch?
一 有扫帚吗
Do they have a broom?
二 有尖鼻子吗
Do they have a pointy nose?
我要笑尿了
I'm… I'm going to pee my pants!
什么 都没有我的角色
So, what, I didn't get the part?
人都去哪了呢
Where's everybody going?
我做了一个超诡异的梦
I just had the most bizarro dream.
什么魔鬼 猩猩 还有一个跳芭蕾的
Demons, apes, a ballet.
您的潜意识非常活跃
You have a very active subconscious.
不管怎样 意识掌管一切
Anyway, the idea took hold.
林德熙·罗翰会过来和你共度春宵
Lindsay Lohan's coming over to spend the night with you.
碉堡了
Awesome!
是你开的
You were driving.